http://westernfiction.com/privacy-policy/

Categories
American Indian (4)
American West (7)
Books Reviews (3)
Old West History (6)
Uncategorized (43)
Western Fiction (11)
Western Movies (1)
Western Products (2)
Writing Western Fiction (3)
Bookmarks
Privacy Policy
Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART CookieGoogle, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Western Books has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Links to third party WebsitesWe have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.
Changes to this Privacy StatementThe contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Western Books then you may contact us at breviapublishing@gmail.com
This policy was generated by Easy Privacy Policy Plugin rac car insurance for WordPress.
Powered by WordPress and WordPress Theme created with Artisteer.
